YOU CAN SEE WE HAD YOU C
DECKED OUT AROUND US DEC
WITH THE BEAUTIFUL
JEFFREY BANKS ITEMS. WE
ARE GOING TO GET YOU ARE
NICE AND SNUGGLED IN. IF
YOU CAN IMAGINE, TAKE A
ROSE PETAL AND PUT IT UP
TO YOUR FACE. NOW TO YOU
IMAGINE WRAPPING YOUR
ENTIRE BODY IN ROSE
PETALS AND BEING ABLE TO
SLEEP THAT WAY EVERY
SINGLE NIGHT. THAT IS
WHAT WE ARE DOING WITH
MICROFIBER. WE HAVE THE
MICROFIBER SHEET SET IN
YOUR CHOICES OF GORGEOUS
COLORS, WE HAD A
BEAUTIFUL SOFT NAVY BLUE,
AS YOU CAN SEE RIGHT
HERE ON THE BED, WE HAVE
A GORGEOUS SOFT GRAY
COLOR. LOOK AT THE SOFT
DREAM COLOR.--GREEN
COLOR, 10, LILAC, PINK,
AND BUTTER GOLD, YOURS
TODAY, $29.95.-- TAN. WE
HAVE FULL, QUEEN, KING,
CALIFORNIA KING IT DOES
NOT MATTER THE SIZE YOU
PAY THE SAME GREAT PRICE,
WELCOME TO ELLEN BUNNER.
WHAT A GREAT VALUE WHA
THESE ARE.
>>GUEST:
>>HOST: THANK YOU KATHY
WOLF CREATE
>>HOST: I LIKE YOUR
>>GUEST: HAIR. THANK
YOU.
>>GUEST: A LOT OF >>GUE
PEOPLE HAVE THE SAME
THOUGHTS WE ALL DID WHEN
WE INTRODUCED
MICROFIBER, $29.95 FOR A
SET, WHAT WERE THEY FEEL
LIKE? THEY FEEL LIKE? TH
FANTASTIC I LOVE YOUR
DESCRIPTION, ROSE PETALS.
THIS IS A NEW FABRIC IT
IS LIKE THE LATEST AND
GREATEST IN TERMS OF
BETTING, IN TERMS OF
SHEETS. NOT ONLY DOES IT
FEEL SO GREAT AND SOFT,
IT IS LIKE A BRUSHED
FEELING EVEN THE WINTER
MONTHS, IT IS GOING TO
FEEL GOOD AGAINST YOUR
SKIN. IT IS HOW IT
PERFORMS, IT IS WRINKLE
RESISTANT, FADE
RESISTANT, SHRINK
RESISTANT, THE EASIEST
LATEST WEEK FABRIC TO
CARE FOR. IT TAKES COLOR
BEAUTIFULLY.
>>HOST: YOU CAN SEE THE
WAY THE STRENGTHS AND
FALLS. IT IS JUST
GORGEOUS.
>>GUEST: I WILL MAKE >>
THE BED A LITTLE BIT. I
WANT YOU TO SEE, IT
FLOATS. IT FLOATS OVER
YOUR BODY. DO YOU SEE YO
THE WAY THAT THIS FALLS?
IT IS THE BEST FEELING.
INITIALLY I BOUGHT THIS
FOR MY KIDS AND EVEN MY
KIDS, TO SEE A
13-YEAR-OLD BOY HE REACT
TO SHEETS ON THE BED, TO
YOU WILL BECOME ADDICTED.
THIS IS AN IVORY, AND
SOME OF THESE COLORS SOM
LIKE YOUR SOFT GOLD I
LIKE HOW THESE ARE NICE
AND MUTED, SO THEY AND M
REALLY ADD TO THAT WHOLE
EXPERIENCE OF THE FEEL
AGAINST YOUR BODY.
>>HOST: NOW THAT IS >>H
YOUR SOFT GOLD.
>>GUEST: LOOK AT THE
LIGHT LILAC, THAT IS
PRETTY I WILL PUT THAT
WITH THE GRAY COLOR. I
THINK THOSE TWO TOGETHER
ARE BEAUTIFUL
COMBINATIONS, THAT IS
PRETTY.
>>HOST: WE DO NOT DO
TWIN SIZE OFTEN WE HAVE
THE TWIN SIZE AVAILABLE
IN THIS COLLECTION. I
CALLED A FRIEND OF MINE
TO LET HER KNOW WE HAVE
THE TWIN SIZE AVAILABLE,
ALL OF THE WAY UP TO
CALIFORNIA KING.
TELEPHONE YOU CAN SHEETS
FOR $29.95 QUESTION MARK
THAT IS UNHEARD OF, YOU
DO NOT FIND THAT, AND IN
YOUR CHOICE OF COLORS.--?
AND THE IVORY IS HARD
TO FIND THIS IS YOUR
PRETTY BEAUTIFUL IVORY
THIS ENABLES YOU TO HAVE
AN EXTRA SET OF SHEETS.
>>GUEST: THIS ENABLES
YOU TO GET YOUR YOU TO G
GUESTROOM READY, THE WAY
THIS FEELS YOU GUESSED
WILL LOVE THE FEEL IF WI
YOU ALWAYS WANT YOUR
GUESTS BED TO FEEL LIKE
A HOTEL, YOU HAVE
ATTEMPTED TO IRON, YOU A
DO NOT NEED TO WORRY
ABOUT THAT WITH THESE,
THESE WILL LOOK FINISHED
IN PRISTINE, GREAT FOR
YOUR KIDS ROOM GREAT FOR
THE FULL DUCK, FOR THE
AIR MATTRESS, THESE ARE
AFFORDABLE, AND ARE SO
AMAZING. WHEN YOU ARE
TALKING ABOUT MICROFIBER,
IT IS A ULTRATHIN FIBER
BUT VERY STRONG, IT IS
100 TIMES FINER THAN A
HUMAN HAIR. IT IS REALLY
FINE, WHEN YOU ARE
TALKING ABOUT A SQUARE
INCH LIKE WE TALK ABOUT
WITH COTTON, THERE ARE
THOUSANDS OF THREADS, IT
IS REALLY A TIGHT WEAVE,
ULTRA SOFT, THIS IS NOT
LIKE THE POLYESTER OF
OLD, WHERE YOU SHOULD DO
A POLYESTER BLEND SHEET
YOU THINK ABOUT CRISPY
AND HARD, WHEN YOU
LAUNDER THEM, THEY GET
BETTER AND BETTER.
>>HOST: LOOK AT THE >>H
JADE COLOR, YOU CAN DO
WITH THE SOFT GRAY OR WI
THE BEAUTIFUL TAUPE. THE
COMBINATION OF THOSE
COLORS, IT IS VERY SPA
AND VERY SERENE.
>>GUEST: ANOTHER PRETTY
COMBINATION WHAT ABOUT
PINK AND GRAY. AND THE
BLUE IS BEAUTIFUL. BLUE
ALMOST LIKE A WEDGEWOOD
BLUE.
>>HOST: A SOFTER SHADE,
LIKE A MARINE BLUE, A
F NAVY BLUE,
REALLY PRETTY. ALMOST
LIKE A DEEP RICH DENIM
COLOR. IT IS LIKE A
PERFECT PAIR OF WORN
JEANS YOU SPEND $90 JE
ONE DOLLARS, EVEN $70 ON
ONE SET OF SHEETS BY THE
TINY FOOT FORBIDS ANY
HOUSE, YOU ARE OVER 1 G.
GRAND. NOW YOU ALWAYS
HAVE A BACKUP SET OF
SHEETS, NO YOU PUT THESE
ON THE BLOWUP HAD. IT IS
A SET OF SHEETS YOU
ALWAYS HAVE ON HAND AND
LACED TO, BECAUSE WE LAC
HAVE THE TWIN SIZE. AND
ALSO, THE FOLDOUT. THIS
IS A SURPRISING
MICROFIBER. IF YOU ARE M
ON THE FENCE AND YOU
NEVER TRIED THIS, THESE
ARE THE SHEETS WE GET AR
FOR HOLIDAY. 11 PEOPLE
HAVE NOT TRIED
MICROFIBER, IT IS VERY
SURPRISING, I CANNOT SUR
EVEN TELL YOU, WHEN I EV
PUT THESE ON MY BED, PUT
THEY BECOME MY FAVORITES.
THEY FEEL SO SOFT
AGAINST HER SKIN. THEY
HAVE A BRUSHED FEEL TO
THEM, IT FEELS LIKE A
ROSE PETAL, FROM TOP TO
BOTTOM FROM THE
PILLOWCASE DOWN TO THE
SHEET, WHEN YOU LAUNDER
THESE, I WISH THERE WAS
A CAMERA IN THESE. THEY
TAKE UP HARDLY ANY TAKE
SPACE, THEY ARE VERY
LIGHTWEIGHT, AND THEY
WERE NO WRINKLES.
>>HOST: DO YOU SEE HOW
FAST THEY DRY QUESTION
MARK IT TAKE 30 MIN. OR
SO, IT WAS NOT EVEN
HALFWAY THROUGH, AND I
WAS LIKE THERE IS NO WAY
THOSE ARE DRY. THEY ARE
DRY, THEY DRY SUPERFAST,
THEY'RE A FANTASTIC BUY.
THEY HAVE ALMOST NO
WRINKLES AT ALL. IF YOU
LEFT THEM IN THERE
BECAUSE YOU PUT THEM BEC
INTO THE DRYER, AND THEY
ARE NOT ALL WRINKLED UP,
YOU DO NOT SPEND MORE
TIME REDRAWING THEM,
THEM,---REDRYING THEM.
>>GUEST: I CAN FILL
THREE SETS OF TWINS
> INSIDE.>HOST: THANK
YOU VICKI FOR SHOPPING
WITH US HAVE YOU EVER WI
TRY THE MICROFIBER TRY T
SHEETS BEFORE?
>>CALLER:
> I HAVE A SET.>HOST: OU
CAME BACK FOR MORE TODAY.
>>CALLER:
>>HOST: YES I HAVE A >>
SET I USE ALL YEAR LONG
I LOVE THESE. WHAT YOU
TELL SOMEBODY WHO HAS
NEVER TRIED MICROFIBER
BEFORE?
>>CALLER: THEY ARE SO
SOFT AND WARM YOU DO NOT
NEED A TON OF BLANKETS N
ON YOUR BED TO GET ONE.
JUST THAT IN A SHEET, JU
THE SHEET AND BLANKET,
HAD A MICROFIBER
BLANKETS, AND I
ABSOLUTELY LOVE THEM.
>>GUEST: THAT IS GREAT
HOW DO YOU LIKE HOW THEY
LAUNDER VICKI? ARE THEY
EASY?
>>CALLER: THEY LAUNDER
JUST EASILY, THEY COME
DOWN AND YOU WRAP
YOURSELF UP IN THESE, YO
AND I JUST LOVE THESE.
>>HOST: THIS IS WHEN >>
YOU GO SNUGGLING IN.
THANK YOU VICKI, I HOPE
YOU ENJOY THE SECOND SET
AS MUCH OF THE FIRST AS
SET. AS VICKI IN UTAH
SAID SHE USES THESE ALL
YEAR LONG AND THEY'RE YE
NOT EVEN TOO HEAVY, BUT
THEY HAVE THAT FEELING
LIKE A REALLY WELL LIKE
WASHED OVER TIME FLANNEL
SHEET, IT HAS THAT KIND
OF FEELING, A SOFT LUSH,
IT IS LIKE A ROSE PETAL.
JUST FEEL A ROSE PETAL
AGAINST YOUR FACE THAT A
IS WHAT YOU HAVE AGAINST
YOUR FACE AND YOUR YOUR
BUDDY, ALL OVER YOUR BUD
BODY EVERY SINGLE DAY.
AND EVERY SINGLE NIGHT
WHEN YOU CRAWL INTO BED,
DO NOT LET THE PRICE DO
FOOL YOU INTO THINKING
YOU ARE GETTING SOMETHING
YOU GET WHAT YOU PAY
FOR. IN THIS CASE YOU FO
GET SO MUCH MORE THAN GE
00:09:56,166
YOU PAID FOR.