<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[Legacy of Hope News]]></title>
    <link>http://legacyofhope.org/news</link>
    <description><![CDATA[Keep up with the Legacy of Hope]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="http://legacyofhope.org/rss/news.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri Oct 17 2014 16:16:57 GMT-0700 (MST)</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Chuck Nice Spotlight]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/10/11/ChuckNice</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[In support of the Legacy of Hope Foundation and the Nelson Mandela Children’s Hospital, Chuck Nice was the emcee for both the 2013 and 2014 Legacy of Hope Mandela Day events held in New York and Los Angeles. At both events, the audience certainly laughed, but they were also given a strong and meaningful message: Nelson Mandela had a final wish. It’s now our turn to work hard and honor this wish and his legacy for future generations.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/10/11/ChuckNice</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Middleweight Boxer Sam Soliman Named Legacy of Hope Ambassador]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/10/5/SamSolimanLOHAmbassador</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Soliman, the Melbourne boxer and former IBF World Middleweight Champion, welcomed the opportunity to align himself with the great South African statesman and humanitarian by becoming an Ambassador for the Legacy of Hope Foundation, a group dedicated to bringing Mandela’s last living wish to fruition.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/10/5/SamSolimanLOHAmbassador</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Arun Gandhi Spotlight]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/10/4/ArunGandhi</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Millions around the world have been influenced and inspired by Nelson Mandela. Of those millions, relatively few met the great South African Leader in person. Arun Gandhi, the fifth grandson of Mahatma Gandhi, was one of those fortunate few.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/10/4/ArunGandhi</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Ruby Bridges Spotlight]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/9/27/RubyBridges</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Ruby Bridges was honored on July 18th, 2014 during the Legacy of Hope Mandela Day Celebration at the Wallis Annenberg Center for the Performing Arts in Beverly Hills. Following this event, Ruby shared her thoughts on what Nelson Mandela meant to her and how a children’s hospital in his name would honor his legacy.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/9/27/RubyBridges</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Táta Vega Spotlight]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/9/20/TataVega</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[In a moving conversation, Táta Vega shared her thoughts following the July 18th, 2014 Legacy of Hope Mandela Day event held at the Wallis Annenberg Center for the Performing Arts, on what would have been Nelson Mandela’s 96th birthday.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/9/20/TataVega</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Youth Ambassador Botlhale Boikanyo]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/9/13/botlhale</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Botlhale Boikanyo is a young, ambitious and inspired Poet from Johannesburg, South Africa. At the age of 11 and well beyond her years in both maturity and insight, Bolthale’s early career was put to test under the bright light auditions of the 2012 South Africa’s Got Talent competition. In that setting, Bolthale’s (pronounced bo-thall-ee) took judges firmly by the heart and walked away the clear and undeniable winner for her gut wrenching and heart lifting prose, inspired by her greatest mentor, Nelson Mandela.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/2014/9/13/botlhale</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Mandela Day 2014]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/mandeladay</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[The Legacy of Hope Foundation hosted an evening of entertainment on Mandela Day to support a global campaign to fulfill the last living wish of Nelson Mandela—to build Africa’s 4th dedicated children’s hospital in Johannesburg, South Africa in 2016. ]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/mandeladay</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[The Gibson Guitar Initiative]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/guitarinitiative</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[The Guitar Initiative is a campaign to increase awareness and support for Nelson Mandela’s Legacy of Hope, through the medium of music. This campaign is supported by Gibson and managed by veteran music producer and executive producer of Legacy of Hope Concerts, Eric Gast. ]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/guitarinitiative</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[The Legacy of Hope Concert]]></title>
      <link>http://legacyofhope.org/concert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Join Legacy of Hope for a worldwide simulcast concert in support of raising $30M for the Nelson Mandela Children’s Hospital. The concert will feature a collection of the world’s most talented and respected musicians and will be broadcast around the world in celebration of Mr. Mandela’s Legacy.]]></description>
      <guid>http://legacyofhope.org/concert</guid>
      <author>Legacy of Hope</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
